[Music] 2
[音乐] 2
[Music] the retractable plan
[音乐]收放方案
[Music]
[音乐]
region - and the inhabitants
地区-居民
[Music] and those of fame
[音乐]和成名的
[Music]
[音乐]
one richard stallman note months ago
几个月前，一位理查德·斯托曼笔记
patagones male bonding tranchettes 28
patagones男性粘合小球28
it's more darling
更亲爱的
[Music] musli
[音乐] musli
[Music] that's why
[音乐]这就是为什么
[Music] the cream friends is on top
[音乐]奶油朋友居首位
[Music] we get sick
[音乐]我们生病了
love letters before in 2008 tyler in your soul
在2008年以前的情书泰勒在你的心灵中
they are still far away, yes, yes, peanuts in the grass
他们还很远，是的
Yes again
再来一次
say if they allow me cello write that
说，如果他们允许我大提琴写
and today serra [Music]
今天是塞拉[音乐]
efe james [Music]
efe james [音乐]
it's bad
这不好
removing rose the edge [Music]
删除玫瑰边缘[音乐]
rubén and the fake for sale new cause
鲁本和待售假货新事业
although the interior of his acts
虽然他行为的内在
I invented [Music]
我发明了[音乐]
and I'm sure it was bone
我确定那是骨头
richard angels ingrid are you going to take effect
理查德·天使·英格里德，你要生效吗
[Music]
[音乐]
me too
我也是
Y
ÿ
by little fockers in changzhou
常州的小福克斯
the appetite for six long seafood
对六种长海鲜的胃口
[Music]
[音乐]
Since I was a child I liked horses and I liked the part of taming, let's say
从我小时候起，我就喜欢骑马，也喜欢驯服。
be able to turn a lover disc horse
能够转过盘马爱好者
Y
ÿ
[Music]
[音乐]
what you have to achieve is to capture the attention of the other
您需要实现的是吸引对方的注意力
whatever it is to scare us until he realizes that if he looks at you or you are and I am
吓到我们的一切，直到他意识到，如果他看着你，或者你是我，我就是
calm and if he is looking the other way there is something that scares him
冷静，如果他在寻找另一种方式，那会吓到他
[Music] wow
[音乐]哇
[Music]
[音乐]
i [Music]
我[音乐]
a [Music]
一个[音乐]
and so much [Music]
还有很多[音乐]
it's an incredible concentration
这是一个令人难以置信的集中
the greatest satisfaction it gives me is power
它给我最大的满足就是力量
walk or ride a horse that later gave me
走路或骑马后来给我的马
industrial smash with 30 rubber dividend football
工业粉碎与30橡胶股息足球
[Music]
[音乐]
of the believers that is to say ingrand
的信徒说恩格朗
You do not get tired
你不累
this great football is further from facebook and white
这个伟大的足球距离Facebook和White更远
[Music] large photo
[音乐]大图
[Music]
[音乐]
and music]
和音乐]
amanda chips when you
当你的阿曼达芯片
[Music] links of units also white since
[音乐]单位链接也为白色
those of all kisses [Music]
所有的吻[音乐]
this [Music]
这个[音乐]
tablecloths how much is it worth
桌布值多少钱
I will sit
我坐
[Music]
[音乐]
[Music] of guests and sectors that I have tried the
我尝试过的[音乐]客人和部门
chipset
芯片组
[Music]
[音乐]
monex break form
monex中断表格
when extra monster lounge
当额外的怪物休息室
your writing to find [Music]
您的写作来寻找[音乐]
I have your profile you do not have removable where many are on this path
我有您的个人资料，您无法移动，这条路径上有很多
Bojan is not joined, the truth is in google's android
Bojan没有加入，事实是在google的android中
today the experience athlete darling office flight options
今天经验丰富的运动员亲爱的办公室的航班选择
[Music] from media between navas steak gardens
[音乐]来自纳瓦斯牛排花园之间的媒体
[Music] when chilemex esment
[音乐] chilemex的时候
we say thinking and his proof
我们说思考和他的证明
lips interaction [Music]
嘴唇互动[音乐]
e [Music]
e [音乐]
that's what james says remaining
这就是詹姆斯说剩下的
[Music]
[音乐]
[Music] next the project is special
[音乐]接下来的项目很特别
of euros
欧元
[Music]
[音乐]
challengers
挑战者
is more they want is intact they sting
他们更希望它们完好无损
[Music]
[音乐]